(Leonard:)You'd think
that the Czech Republic
(Sheldon(on screen):)would try to hold on
to what it had,
(Sheldon(on screen):)given that it's not as young
as it used to be.
(Sheldon(on screen):)And I don't see
any other countries
(Sheldon(on screen):)lining up to invade
its southern borders.
(Amy:)I'm gonna kill him.
(Sheldon:)But enough
about the Czech Republic.
(Sheldon:)Let's talk about the time
Moldova made Romania
(Sheldon:)a birthday cake
and Romania said it tasted good
(Sheldon:)even though it didn't.
(Sheldon:)And yet Romania gets dumped.
(Sheldon:)I'll pause here
while you mull that one over.
(Sheldon:)I know, right?
(Penny:)So, you said you had
something to tell me.
(Leonard:)Okay, yeah, um,
(Leonard:)do you remember
when you accused me
(Leonard:)of trying to sabotage
our wedding?
(Penny:)Uh-huh.
(Leonard:)I've been thinking about it,
and you might be right.
(Leonard:)But the good news is
that I'm pretty sure I know why.
(Penny:)I'm listening.
(Leonard:)Penny, after all these years,
(Leonard:)I still feel like
maybe I don't deserve you.